I can tell you that brother you are crazy.
I'm saying I'm going I'm going Man.
05:30 tô there then beauty gratitude for the opportunity saw bro?
I owe it to me to speak.
I unroll my tapes.
not not for
to even the rope.
if I had rope
I discovered the problem of red chevas
that happened.
Oh oh the screws here you see here,
right where are the screws here?
O joint out o party o o have to play together
so it won't work it never will right?
I have to work today.
Catch a job at the restaurant O Marcelo brigadão eh?
Hand?
Save some money.
The chevas are giving a lot of embezzlement but you can't stand still.
So I don't know how much the bewilderment of the car will cost.
Make some beaks there to be able to guarantee it,
right?
Malandro
i ng quyn hông thôi
Give you 1 money ah bro you're crazy huh?
Good cheer for us and my partners over there from the gas station.
Hand.
I didn't want to charge man because we had a pistachio pancake yesterday.
Fall. Relax.
I don't do that but relationship makes us open the door.
Is it on now?
I'm here in an ember that I'm leaving the truffles and they're
needing people to be able to make a trap today.
And I'm going to do a half-faced little foot if I'm elderly.
Something there?
Park here.
Preferential.
Come by kindness thank you.
Have you seen this whole area?
Te help comes more more more can IR can IR.
This is now just straightening
one more.
Hello good night how are you doing?
Alright,
you can go put gear,
watch out for the wheel on the side.
Okay worth it the bad side is sometimes you do it that way.
Good night then the person doesn't answer pô
people cost a good night for the valet.
VIP service with cannon.
Let me get the people for you here.
Imagine everything well dear.
Valet diary.
The time does not pass.
Bye guys,
good night.
All I put these cars all here.
Another little while they left they came back and I'm cold with hungry rain.
And that's it bro.
See you tomorrow.